[{"id": 1, 
  "type": "input",
  "question": "He wants to get a better ______ and earn more money.",
  "rightAnswer": ["job"]}, 
  {"id": 2, 
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": " Managers set objectives, and decide ______ their organization can achieve them.",
    "answers":  ["what", "how", "which", "because"], 
    "rightAnswer": ["how"]}, 
  {"id": 3, 
    "type": "radio",
    "question": "Obviously, objectives occasionally ______ be modified or changed.",
    "answers": ["must", "have to", "ought to", "shouldn't"], 
    "rightAnswer": ["have to"]}, 
  {"id": 4, 
    "type": "input",
    "question": "Managers who are ambitious are ____________ -oriented managers.",
    "rightAnswer": ["success"]}, 
  {"id": 5, 
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": "You won’t be allowed into the club ______ you wear a suit and tie.",
    "answers": ["unless", "if", "whether", "when"], 
    "rightAnswer": ["unless"]}, 
  {"id": 6, 
    "type": "radio",
    "question": "We haven’t had ______ news from our agent.",
    "answers": ["any", "no", "some", "none"], 
    "rightAnswer": ["any"]}, 
  {"id": 7, 
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": "I’ve lost my keys. I can’t find them ______.",
    "answers": ["nowhere", "anywhere", "everywhere", "somewhere"], 
    "rightAnswer": ["anywhere"]}, 
  {"id": 8, 
    "type": "input",
    "question": "I haven’t seen your cousin _____ ages.", 
    "rightAnswer": ["for"]}, 
  {"id": 9, 
    "type": "radio",
    "question": "We'll never get to the airport! There is ______ time!",
    "answers": ["too few", "too little", "too much little", "too much few"], 
    "rightAnswer": ["too little"]}, 
  {"id": 10, 
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": "When do we use the Simple Past?",
    "answers": ["actions finished in the past", "series of completed actions in the past", "for something that started in the past and continues in the present"],
    "rightAnswer": ["actions finished in the past", "series of completed actions in the past"]}]